the-best-apps.net 2018-06-27

# mobusi - Privacy Policy

The purpose of this Privacy and Cookie Policy (hereafter, the “Policy”) is to regulate Mobusi Mobile Advertising, S.L.´s data processing activities (hereinafter MOBUSI). MOBUSI provides advanced solutions, which are compatible with all common standards which simplifies the management of advertising campaigns. These solutions enable MOBUSI to offer the best campaigns to each user. Said activities are conducted through the website www.mobusi.com (hereinafter, the **“Website”** ). This Policy also sets the conditions for the installation of cookies in MOBUSI user or data subject’s browser (hereinafter, the **“User”** ).

This Policy may be supplemented by any specific provisions that may be established to regulate the processing of specific personal data.

**1.  MOBUSI’s processing of Personal Data**

In compliance with EU Regulation 2016/679 on Data Protection (“GDPR”), MOBUSI will process Personal Data that is collected through contact forms, contracting of services or any other means related to the Website. As such, MOBUSI will be referred to as the Data Controller. User’s personal data that is collected will be treated with absolute confidentiality and in compliance with the duty of secrecy. 

Likewise, MOBUSI informs its Users that the collected personal data will be stored in a Record of Processing Activities that is solely owned by MOBUSI. MOBUSI has implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure the security of your personal data and to prevent said data from its destruction, loss, unlawful access or unlawful alteration. In determining these measures, MOBUSI has taken into account the scope, context, and purpose of the treatment; the current state of the art and the risks involved to develop said measures.

**2.  Purposes for which MOBUSI processes Personal Data**

In compliance with the principles of privacy by design, privacy by default and data minimisation, MOBUSI will only collect the personal data that is necessary for achieving the below indicated purposes. As a matter of fact, the personal data that is collected through the Website is relevant, adequate and not excessive in accordance with said purposes. MOBUSI does not use illegal, unfair or fraudulent procedures to obtain personal data.

The main purpose for which MOBUSI collects personal data is to provide information about services or registration of Users who access MOBUSI’s Website to either consult: (i) additional generic information related to MOBUSI or; (ii) specific information related to the User’s own activity. Likewise, if the User expressly consent, MOBUSI may process his or her data to send informative communications that are related to MOBUSI’s activity, offers, events, and future services. These communications may be send by email.

MOBUSI will request the User’s prior consent every time his or her data is used for a different purpose than that for which it was provided or requested. 

**3.  Rights that Users may exercise before MOBUSI or the relevant Supervisory Authority**

Any User who wishes to exercise his or her rights of access, rectification, erasure, restriction of the processing, to data portability or of objection must notify MOBUSI upon written request send to the email address: [gdpr@mobusi.com](mailto:gdpr@mobusi.com) or to MOBUSI’s headquarters, located at C/ Quintana 2, 2ª Planta 28008 - Madrid. In accordance with GDPR provisions, the contents of the rights that Users are entitled to are the following:

  * Right of access: The user can request MOBUSI to disclose which data relating to him or she is subject to processing by MOBUSI as well as the source from which the data was collected and the purpose for which the data is being processed.
  * Right to rectification: The User can request MOBUSI to modify any personal data that is not updated.
  * Right to erasure: The User can request MOBUSI to delete his or her personal data unless there are justified and valid reasons that allow MOBUSI to maintain the data. The Right of Erasure implies a period whereby the personal data will remained blocked in order to comply with any legal obligations that may arise before its definitive deletion.
  * Right of objection: The User can object before MOBUSI its use of personal data for certain purposes. 
  * Right to restrict the processing: The User can request MOBUSI to highlight its personal data as being restricted to the specific purposes that the User accepted. 
  * Right to data portability: The User can request MOBUSI to provide him or her with the information that MOBUSI holds in an interoperable computer-friendly format.
  * Right to file a complaint before the relevant Supervisory Authority: In the event of disagreement with the way MOBUSI collects and processes personal data or have addressed requests for the exercise of User rights, the Users may file a complaint before the Supervisory Authority (Agencia Española de Protección de Datos).

MOBUSI shall comply with any User right requests within a maximum period of 30 days since the rights were exercised. MOBUSI informs that this period could be extended to maximum 90 days upon valid justification.

**4.  Third party recipients that may have access to User personal data**

MOBUSI undertakes not to transfer or communicate User personal data to any third party unless prior and explicit authorisation by the User.

Nevertheless, it is possible that MOBUSI allows access to User personal data to third parties that provide a relevant service to the User. These third parties will acquire the status of Data Processors. As such, they may only process User personal data in accordance with MOBUSI’s instructions. Under no circumstances will Data Processors use User personal data for other purpose than those that are detailed in Section 2 of this Policy.

**5.  Cookies**

This Website uses its own cookies and those of third parties that are necessary to allow the User enjoy all the functionalities of the Website as well as monitoring and control User activity in the Website. Cookies are small text files that are installed in the User’s browser and which are used to record his or her activity on the Website, to allow more fluid and personalized web browsing or to provide additional functionalities such as the viewing of interactive videos or graphics or to enable access to the User’s private profile. 

Users may configure and order their browser to not accept cookies, block them and, if necessary, delete them. In accordance with article 22(2) of Spanish Act 34/2002 (“LSSI”), the User may refuse to install cookies when accessing the Website. However, MOBUSI informs you that some of its Website functions demand the installation of cookies in order for it to function correctly. As such, Users understand that uninstalling or refusing cookies could limit their web browsing activities.

This Website installs the following cookies:

**COOKIE** | **Purpose** | **OWN OR THIRD PARTY COOKIE**  
---|---|---  
PHPSESSID | Session Cookie | Own cookie  
mob_lang; lang | To determine user language  | Own cookie  
mob_soze | To improve users security | Own cookie  
_ga; _gat | To distinguish between different users | Google analytics  
gid | To limit request percentage | Google analytics  
AMP_TOKEN | Includes a token that can be used to retrieve a customer ID from the AMP | Google analytics  
_gac_>property-id< | Coordinates users information with google analytics and Adwords accoutns  | Google analytics  
  
**Changing The Web Browser Preferences**

You can change the preferences of your browser to choose which cookies it must allow access to. These preferences are usually in the menu "options" or "preferences" of your browser.

You can find more information here, or in the menu "Help" of your browser:

Internet Explorer: Tools > Internet Options > Configuration. For more information, consult Microsoft support or the Help tab.

Firefox: Tools > Options > Privacy > History > Personalized Configuration. For more information, consult Mozilla Support or the Help tab. 

Chrome: Configuration > Show Advanced Options > Privacy > Content Configuration. For more information consult Google Support or the Help tab. 

Safari: Preferences > Security. For more information, consult Apple Support or the Help tab.

However, if you change your preferences and block these cookies, some functions of our Website will be annulled and you will not be able to make the most of the features from our Website.
